so now that we are done with the work
for cycle 4 let's see what happens in
cycle 5 two things will happen in cycle
5 one is we're going to try to issue the
next instruction another thing is we're
going to try to see if we can dispatch
an instruction write a result or
commit obviously we can issue this
instruction so let's do that so the
question for you is do we dispatch an
instruction right here which instruction
gets dispatched leave it empty if none
of them gets dispatched another question
for you is do we write any results in
this cycle if yes write which
instruction gets to write the results if
no just leave this empty and obviously
we won't be committing any instructions
the name of the instruction here should
be the really the Rob entry so if it's
for example the Rob one instruction that
gets dis patch you should write Rob one
here